Dragon Balls.
When seven of these
mysterious balls are gathered
and the password recited,
a dragon called Shenron appears.
Shenron will grant
whatever wish is requested.
This man, Son Goku, may appear gentle,
but is the most powerful warrior
who possesses unworldly strength.
He lived in the mountains as a child,
searched for the Dragon Balls,
met many friends,
and went on adventures with them
as he grew into adulthood.
One day, a vicious battle race
called Saiyans arrived.
Goku learned that he, too, was a Saiyan
who was sent to Earth as an infant.
Saiyans maintain a youthful body
for much of their lives.
Goku continues to face terrifying enemies
and grows through his battles.
And together, with his former rivals,
he continues
to protect the Earth from evil.
Now, the Earth faces a new threat…
CONSPIRACY
Original Work, Story & Character Design
Akira Toriyama (Shueisha "Jump comics”)
Curse that Babidi!
That crafty little scoundrel!
He actually used King Dabura.
I can't believe the Supreme Demon King
would fall prey to Babidi's magic.
How disgraceful.
Dabura… Is he strong or somethin'?
Of course he is.
He's the king of the dark demon world.
K-King of the demon world?!
Such a world exists?
It does.
Look at that, Degesu.
Isn't that your older brother?
Still the nosey upstart as always.
He thinks so highly of himself
as Supreme Kai.
He's not helping the mortals, is he?
Let's look a little further ahead.
You idiot…!
What in the world?!
How can such powerful beings exist
in the outside world?!
Do you think they could be Majin?
They can't be. Look.
Their ears are round.
But they're flying.
They fire light from their hands…
and seem to be able to use magic.
At last, Majin Buu awakens again!
Buu!
And now Buu is back!
Curse that Babidi.
He wants to rule
not only the outside world,
but the Demon Realm and all worlds, too.
I think I'll eat you.
Look! Dabura was defeated!
And so easily!
And now you're
the king of the Demon Realm.
No, no, no, no, no!
We can't be celebrating!
The next target that Babidi is going to
use Majin Buu on is us!
You're right.
Lord Gomah! Isn't that a Namek?
Huh?
Now that you mention it…
They did it! They defeated Buu!
We'll see.
I knew he was still alive.
Hey! The sky went dark!
What could be happening?
Hmm?
Could it be…?
Found it! This is the reason!
Look! Th-Those are Dragon Balls!
Dragon Balls?!
See?!
Those ball-like things they have there!
I'm sure of it!
They're smaller, but they're Dragon Balls!
One… Two… Three… Four… There are seven.
I can't believe it!
Theirs are composed of seven Balls!
But this looks quite different
from the Porunga I've read about.
Let's rewind a bit!
Rise, Shenron!
So they seem to call it Shenron
instead of Porunga.
From the way they seem to be used to this,
their Dragon Balls must be easy to gather.
Now speak your wish.
I shall grant any three wishes you have.
Three?!
On Earth they get three whole wishes?!
This is a huge discovery!
Hold on. What happened with Buu?
I don't need you anymore!
Die! Dummy!
He killed him?!
Buu kill his own master Babidi!
This is glorious!
We lost him?! Where is he?!
Look at that! Another Namek!
Yeah! There's no mistake!
No wonder we couldn't find any
despite searching.
They escaped to the outside world.
Buu's changed!
It looks like Buu has increased in power.
Death Missile Chain!
What is with these
unbelievably powerful beings?!
H-Here we go!
See you!
I can't believe it.
They actually defeated Majin Buu!
Everyone who would
stand in your way is gone.
And now you have become king of
the Demon Realm in both name and reality.
Congratulations, King Gomah.
Sister…!
Excuse me. You're here, too, Degesu?
Hello, Dr. Arinsu.
You're looking as beautiful as ever.
Why thank you.
How goes your research?
It's going quite splendidly.
More importantly, congratulations.
I see we have a new Supreme Demon King.
How did you know?
It seems my older sister was also watching
from somewhere.
It's not like King Dabura
to go to the outside world is it?
It piqued my curiosity.
Isn't that the same as you two?
Well, I guess that's true.
Still, it's unfortunate for you!
King Dabura may have given you
all the research funding you wanted,
but he's been murdered.
Oh? As king, you're going to
continue to fund my research aren't you?
We'll see about that.
You may want to be careful, though.
I mean, who wouldn't be?
They defeated the legendary Majin Buu.
If such people were to invade
the Demon Realm…
I shiver at the thought!
There's no need to worry.
There's no reason why they would risk
the dangers of coming to the Demon Realm.
We can only hope.
Now if you'll excuse me…
"King Gomah."
Will we really be okay?
What?
If such beings really came here,
that would be bad, wouldn't it?
You shouldn't listen to
the ramblings of my sister.
Even if they ever come to the Demon Realm,
they'd never reach this Demon King Palace.
That's it.
Let's use the Dragon Balls!
The Dragon Balls?! Are you serious?
The three powerful Tamagamis protect them.
Not the Dragon Balls of the Demon Realm.
The small Dragon Balls
of that planet Earth.
Earth's?
That's right. You saw it, didn't you?
Those Dragon Balls
might be easy to gather.
But what will you wish for?
I'm sure their power
is based in white magic,
so I doubt a black wish like
eliminating them will be accepted.
I know that!
We make them young.
What?
That's not a black wish, is it?
That's quite ingenious.
Y-You're still here?!
It'd be nice if you made me young as well.
Make them young?
Th-That's right.
Basically we turn them all into children
to make them harmless.
I see! So we weaken them drastically!
There you have it.
And for my second wish…
Let's get the Evil Third Eye!
The Evil Third Eye!
You mean the legendary Tertian Oculus?!
It was lost during the reign of
Dabura's father, Supreme Demon King Abura.
That's right.
Placing it on the forehead is said to
grant unbelievable power.
Since long ago, it was passed down
among the Supreme Demon Kings,
granting them absolute power!
Indeed it would be
the absolute item to obtain.
Right? And for my third wish…
Please, if I could be given
at least one wish.
Hmm?
I'll consider it.
I'll be busy with my coronation party,
and making speeches in the three
Demon Worlds and appealing to the Majin.
We'll execute my plan after that.
Have my vessel ready.
Understood, sire.
Ah, I'll be bringing Neva the Namek.
He's a little senile, but no one knows
more about the Dragon Balls.
Yes, sire.
Hurry up!
Walk faster!
Curses! There's a Dragon Ball right here!
But the darn Tamagami is, too!
Hey, good work.
Now hurry up and get in the plane.
Now, now. Don't rush me.
Something smells.
When was the last time you took a shower?
A shower? I think I took one years ago
when I fell in the mud.
Hey, Degesu!
Switch places with me! I'm piloting!
-But…!
-Hurry up!
-Hold on!
-Hurry up and switch!
Where are you taking me?
Like I said, the outside world.
We aren't supposed to go to outside world.
We've already done all the proceedings.
Is this a vacation?
Turn around.
I forgot my toothbrush.
We'll come right back!
We're going to go see a young Namek
for some business!
A Namek? That sounds wonderful.
Other Nameks still exist!
Who goes there? Identify yourself.
The new Supreme Demon King Gomah!
You can call me King Gomah!
Well good for you.
You can spare me the details.
Just say the pin number.
0493.
What?!
So you're going to the outside world…
Very well. I suppose I'll let you go.
That's all?!
So you're going to the outside world?
Which universe?
Universe 7.
What number in Universe 7?
Which is closest to Earth…?
Number 3.
You want to go to number 3?
That's been popular, recently.
Popular?
You mean Dabura and Babidi.
Someone else went there after them.
What?! Who?! Tell me their name!
You're an arrogant one!
I-I'm sorry.
Tell me… please.
I think it was Dr. Arinsu.
My sister?!
Why would she do that?
She better not be up to something.
Stop wasting time and just go!
You're the one who brought it up.
Trunks, happy birthday!
And congratulations
to the Earth returning!
Cheers!
Thanks!
Hey Trunks, how old are you now?
I'm nine.
Nine, huh?
You're a little short for being nine.
You're one to talk.
Saiyans get a growth spurt at around 15.
Yeah, that happened with you, didn't it?
Well, I guess Vegeta didn't get that big.
Are you picking a fight?
Huh? Supreme Kai-sama!
What are you doin' here?
Well… I had some other business…
Huh? Didn't you two
fuse with your Potaras?
I thought it couldn't be undone!
How'd you do it?!
You and Vegeta-san fused with the Potaras,
but when you were absorbed by Majin Buu,
for some reason
it was undone and you split apart again.
We remembered that
and asked Buu-san to try it again.
When I inhaled them and spit them out,
they were separated.
It appears that Majin Buu's body produces
a mysterious gas
that can reverse a Potara fusion.
Oh come on.
So you didn't really wanna fuse after all?
Well, Kibito is a little old, so…
You never cease to amaze, Goku.
You actually asked Shenron to make Buu
a good guy and let him remain on Earth.
It doesn't look like Gohan-san is here.
Gohan's bein' a little distant.
He said he's busy studyin'.
I suppose he couldn't study much
with all the fighting.
I'm stuffed!
Now that I've had my fill…
Vegeta, wanna train?
Very well.
And there they go again all of a sudden.
Just ignore them.
Ain't you gettin' carried away?
They seem to be having fun.
Shall we join them?
We can't. There's no telling
what can happen at any time.
You're right. Something happened.
We finally made it!
Wh-Who are you?
Oh!
It really is a Namek.
I haven't seen a fellow Namek
in thousands of years.
Are you one of the Supreme Kai?
Not exactly.
We came from the Demon Realm.
As did your ancestors, correct?
See? Your ears are pointy.
You're from the Demon Realm, too.
Move!
Can I help you?
I suppose I'll ask.
You manage
the Dragon Balls of this world, right?
In that case bring them all here.
The Dragon Balls?! I can't do that!
I figured you'd say that.
Good thing I brought this old geezer.
Hey! Do it.
Do what?
We went over this!
I'll extend your life 1,000 years,
so gather the Earth Dragon Balls!
Ah yes. Right…
Who… Who is that…?
The Demon Realm has its own Dragon Balls.
He's the one who made them long ago.
But he also…
created terrifying beings called Tamagamis
to protect the balls,
so for the longest time
no one has had a wish granted.
But we heard that Earth has some,
and that's why we're here.
Wait. Do you intend to use
our Dragon Balls to make a wish?!
Of course I do.
Ah… It looks like
they've granted a wish recently and
are still turned into stones.
This'll be hard to find.
Th-That's…!
One, two, three, four…
Seven!
-Good. Let's begin.
-Neva.
You can restore the Dragon Balls
sooner than normal, right?
I don't know what your wish is, but
I'll die before I tell you the password!
We watched a video of you and took notes.
Rise, Shen--
Stop!
Is there a problem?
Um… Would you like some juice?
No thank you.
Rise, Shenron!
And grant my wish!
Huh? What's going on?
Everything went dark.
Could it be that Shenron was summoned…?
That's not possible.
The Dragon Balls should still be rocks.
I didn't hear about an eclipse.
I wonder what it is.
Supreme Kai-sama.
Kibito, did you sense that, too?
That presence…
Now speak your wish.
I will grant any wish.
Wonderful! Well, let's see…
Turn the ones who fought Majin Buu
and all their friends into children!
Well? What's wrong?!
By children, how old do you mean?
Huh?!
Let me think… Maybe first graders?
And for those who are already children?
You're pretty picky.
Well…
Make them babies!
Well?!
You said you'd grant any wish, right?!
Very well.
Hee, hee hee!
Time to adventure!
You'll be hooked for sure!
The Demon Realm is full of mystery
DAIMA wonderland
Whoopsie daisy!
Even when your heart shrinks
And you feel low
Dreams are everywhere
Don't worry about it
Never give up
Here comes a New Story
Thousands of jabs and silly jokes
They're waitin' for you
Jaan! Jaka jaan!
The fanfare of courage
No-holds-barred battles
The excitement ain't stoppin'
Hey Shenron, grant my wish
I wanna meet
Someone amazin' again tomorrow
GLORIO